Giulio V. Blanc
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Subject Files, 1933-1995, undated, Series 5:; (boxes 8-12; 2.5 linear feet)
  - Latin American Art in the 20th Century, E. J. Sullivan, editor, 1994, (5 folders) (Box 12 (pam), Reel 5487)
  - Memoria project, undated (Box 12 (pam), Reel 5487)
- Untranscribed Sound Recordings, 1992-1994, Series 6:; (box 12; 2 folders)
  - Sound recording, audio cassette tape of College Art Association session: Artistic Voices of Latin America: The Aesthetics of Anti-Colonialism, Chicago, IL, 1992 Giulio V. Blanc, panelist (Box 12 (pam), Reel unfilmed)
  - Sound recording, interview conducted by Blanc with Monseñor Angel Gaztelu, Miami, FL, 1994 (Box 12 (pam), Reel unfilmed)
- Photographs, 1981, 1993, undated, Series 7:; (box 12; 2 folders)
  Large black and white portraits of artists René Portocarrero, Mariano Rodríguez, and Rufino Tamayo. Black and white photographs of Blanc with Cuban artists María Brito, Carlos Macía, María Martínez Cañas, Pablo Cano, Arturo Rodríguez, and César Trasobares. Group photograph with the Scull sisters, Consuelo Castañeda, Tomás Sanchez, José Bedia, Connie Lloveras, Tomás Esson, and others.
  - Photographs, 1981, 1993 (Box 12 (pam), Reel 5487)
  - Photographs, undated (Box 13 (sol), Reel 5487)
  - Oversized Material from Series 5: Subject Files, 1933-1995 (Box 14 (ov), Reel unfilmed)